<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Graphitedge</title>
    <link>https://graphitedge.com.au/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Graphitedge</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2017 12:26:26 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://graphitedge.com.au/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>CONVERSATIONS WITH YOUR WEB DEVELOPER, DESIGNER, AGENCY: Part 2</title>
      <link>https://graphitedge.com.au/post/what-your-developer-needs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2017 12:26:26 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://graphitedge.com.au/post/what-your-developer-needs/</guid>
      <description>If you have not already seen it, take a look at part 1 of this series.
What your web developer, designer, or agency needs from you So you are ready to start a your conversation with your web technologist. Great! There are somethings that you can prepare before hand to help them give you the best advice, design and help. # more Firstly, provide information about what your business actually does.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CONVERSATIONS WITH YOUR WEB DEVELOPER, DESIGNER, AGENCY: Part 1</title>
      <link>https://graphitedge.com.au/post/what-developer-needs-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2017 12:54:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://graphitedge.com.au/post/what-developer-needs-part-1/</guid>
      <description>Have you gone through a website build only to not have your requirements not met? Have you been looking for someone to build your website, yet find that there is often too high a price to pay? Have you had a web designer, developer or agency string you along and not delivered? Have you gone into a website build only to discover what was not delivered was not what you required?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Responsive Development</title>
      <link>https://graphitedge.com.au/service/service3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://graphitedge.com.au/service/service3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;And if that sounds not like your ballpark then Helen is able to take your site mockups and using various techniques in CSS and HTML (with or without frameworks) to create and deploy a responsive website for you.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Site Security</title>
      <link>https://graphitedge.com.au/service/service4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://graphitedge.com.au/service/service4/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;With Security being the topic of the moment, have Helen take a look at the security of your site via a Security Site Checkup. Helen can then advise you on how to keep your website and clients safe.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web Mastery</title>
      <link>https://graphitedge.com.au/service/service1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://graphitedge.com.au/service/service1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Site Maintainer YOU need.
Since website downtime can be a costly thing for your business, Helen is able guide you through being a novice to web master in how to keep your site up and running.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wordpress Consultation</title>
      <link>https://graphitedge.com.au/service/service2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://graphitedge.com.au/service/service2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As Matt Mullenweg has stated that he is looking to have 50% of all website run by WordPress, the need for guidance to have an effective site using Wordpress is ever increasing. Helen provides this guidance and builds sites according to an agreed scope.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life was simple once ...</title>
      <link>https://graphitedge.com.au/post/life-was-simple-once/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2013 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://graphitedge.com.au/post/life-was-simple-once/</guid>
      <description>The pervasiveness of the technological age. A telephone was a device for conversation between two people. People wrote letters when they had finished writing they put them in the mailbox. A car may have a radio in it; most cars did have one at all.
Now we have all this “stuff” that is connected. Connected in multiple ways as well. We have a phone that can bring the world to our fingertips.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://graphitedge.com.au/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://graphitedge.com.au/about/</guid>
      <description>GraphitEdge is Helen Burgess and Helen Burgess is GraphitEdge.
The Story behind the logo and name Helen&amp;rsquo;s nickname for the longest time as HB as in HB pencil. This spurred the idea to call her business Graphite Edge. Well, why Graphite Edge? Most of the best names for having a sharp pencil were already taken and by talking with some of her industry besties, Helen decided to take a twist on the name.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WordPress Course for Codemaster Institute</title>
      <link>https://graphitedge.com.au/recent-works/0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://graphitedge.com.au/recent-works/0/</guid>
      <description>The creation and recording of video for the Go WordPress Online Course that takes students from installing on both the local and remote environments through to adding in Woo Commerce plus configuring it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>